999 MAIN STREET, ANY TOWN, NY 99999; email: email@yahoo.com

Business Analyst Consultant

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Senior Software Developer and Business Analyst, with expertise in improving business decision making by navigating, automating and developing reporting applications for Finance, Online payments, Merchant Services and Sales systems. Established history of achieving goals through insightful listening, working as a problem solver, active team member and a recognized team lead. Consistently ranked in top quartile on performance reviews

QUALIFICATIONS

Business Intelligence Tools: Brio6 (Hyperion Desktop), Business Objects, Micro strategy 7.5.3,

Informatica Power Analyzer, SalesForce.Com

Database Tools: Oracle 8i/9i, SQL*Plus, PL/SQL, Sybase 10, T-SQL, Teradata/BTEQ

Languages/Scripting: Perl, Shell Script, C, Pascal, COBOL

Other Tools: Clear Case, CVS, Essbase Manager, PowerBuilder, Visual Basic,

Informatics PowerCenter 6.2

Operating Systems: Solaris, UNIX, Windows

EXPERIENCE

ABC Inc., Any Town, ny (3/2007 - PRESENT)

Finance Business Analyst Consultant

- Manage accounting activities related to revenue recognition and revenue assurance processes.
- Ensure revenue transfer activities comply with SOX requirements and Corporate Revenue Policies.
- Monitor, approve, and provide reporting on financial transactions.

XYZ Corp., Any Town, NY (1999- 2006)

Business Operations/Procurement

- Assisted in the implementation of a automated time keeping system including proof of concept, training development, and change management.
- Provided assistance in the Pre-Audit of financial information for SEC compliance.

BCD Inc., Any Town, Ny (1997-1999)

Sr. Business Analyst

- Strategic development of business solutions.
- Evaluated and documented business requirements.
- Created and documented process descriptions and process flows as well as robust use cases.
- Conducted extensive research to establish and document industry-wide best practices with respect to tools and procedures are used.
- Performed gap analyses of CORE requirements and new product development initiatives.
- Participated in strategy sessions with senior members of the Management, to assess current product functionality and establish the extent of a development effort to create new solutions.

Richard Martin

EDUCATION

University of New York – 1990 Training in SalesForce.Com

EFFINE CAREER COACH. COM